♪♪♪
♪ UHH UHH ♪
♪ I, I JUST WOKE UP
FROM A DREAM ♪
♪ WHERE YOU AND I HAD
TO SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AND I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT ALL MEANS ♪
♪ BUT SINCE I SURVIVED
I REALIZED ♪
♪ WHEREVER YOU GO
THAT'S WHERE I'LL FOLLOW ♪
♪ NOBODY’S PROMISED TOMORROW ♪
♪ SO IMMA LOVE YOU EVERY NIGHT
LIKE IT'S THE LAST NIGHT ♪
♪ LIKE IT’S THE LAST NIGHT ♪
♪ IF THE WORLD WAS ENDING
I’D WANNA BE NEXT (TO YOU) ♪
♪ IF THE PARTY WAS OVER AND OUR
TIME ON EARTH (WAS THROUGH) ♪
♪ I’D WANNA HOLD YOU
JUST FOR A WHILE ♪
♪ AND DIE WITH A SMILE ♪
♪ IF THE WORLD WAS ENDING
I’D WANNA BE NEXT TO YOU ♪
♪ (WOO OOH) ♪
♪ OOH LOST ♪
♪ LOST IN THE WORDS
THAT WE SCREAM ♪
♪ I DON'T EVEN WANNA
DO THIS ANYMORE ♪
[DUO] ♪ CUZ YOU ALREADY
KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN TO ME ♪
♪ AND OUR LOVE IS THE ONLY
WAR WORTH FIGHTING FOR ♪
♪ WHEREVER YOU GO
THAT'S WHERE I'LL FOLLOW ♪
♪ NOBODY’S PROMISED TOMORROW ♪
♪ SO IMMA LOVE YOU EVERY NIGHT
LIKE IT’S THE LAST NIGHT ♪
♪ LIKE IT’S THE LAST NIGHT ♪
♪ IF THE WORLD WAS ENDING
I’D WANNA BE NEXT TO YOU ♪
♪ IF THE PARTY WAS OVER ♪
♪ AND OUR TIME ON EARTH
WAS THROUGH ♪
♪ I’D WANNA HOLD YOU ♪
♪ JUST FOR A WHILE ♪
♪ AND DIE WITH A SMILE ♪
♪ IF THE WORLD WAS ENDING
I’D WANNA BE NEXT TO YOU ♪
♪ RIGHT NEXT TO YOU ♪
♪ NEXT TO YOU ♪
♪ [BOTH VOCALIZING] ♪
♪♪♪
♪ IF THE WORLD WAS ENDING
I’D WANNA BE NEXT (TO YOU) ♪
♪ IF THE PARTY WAS OVER
AND OUR TIME ON EARTH
(WAS THROUGH) ♪
♪ I’D WANNA HOLD YOU
JUST FOR A WHILE ♪
♪ AND DIE WITH A SMILE ♪
♪ IF THE WORLD WAS ENDING
I’D WANNA BE NEXT TO YOU ♪
♪♪♪
♪ [VOCALIZING] ♪
♪ I’D WANNA BE NEXT TO YOU ♪